# Collin Dapper

Tracy, Ca 95376 | (510)-599-3461 | collindapper@gmail.com

Website: <a href="https://www.collindapper.com/">https://www.collindapper.com/</a>

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/collin-dapper-a1b59a152/

GitHub: https://github.com/collindapper

#### **SUMMARY**

Adaptive and creative junior full-stack web developer with proficiency in front-end programming languages such as: HTML, CSS, and ReactJS; Back-end programming knowledge in JavaScript and Ruby, as well as, conducting user research and collaborating with developers to build dynamic websites. Professional strengths include problem-solving, communication and time management. Analytical and leadership mindset from experience in Operations Management.

#### **SKILLS**

Management
Team Leadership
JavaScript
Ruby on Rails
Full-Stack Development
React.js
REST APIs
Juanguage (HTML)
JQuery
Dynamic Websites
Cascading Style Sheets
Data Analysis
Ruby Programming

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Altcademy | November 2021 - September 2022

Full-Stack Web Development Certification

## University of Nevada, Reno | January 2018 - August 2020

- Bachelor of Science in Business Administration, Finance. Minor in Economics.

## San Joaquin Delta College | June 2015 - December 2018

Associates in Math and Science (AA-T) / Associates in Business Administration (AS-T)

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Full-Stack Web Developer (Student) | Altcademy | November 2021 - Current

- Developed three user-friendly websites using React JS and JavaScript, along with several other programming languages, libraries and frameworks.
- Created a full-stack, ReactJS and Ruby on Rails, social media website. Personally created the Front-End and layout, as well as, creating the API and API endpoints. The build allows users to create a profile, see other users posts, as well as post messages and images to their own feeds.
- Created a full-stack, ReactJS and Ruby on Rails, online marketplace. Developed the Front-End and layout, as well as, creating the API and API endpoints. The build allows users to create properties via listings (add, edit, delete and create property listings), and book trips off of other users listings via Stripe web-hook for transactions.

#### Manager I, Operations | Amazon.com | April 2021 - April 2022

- Coach, manage, and develop a team of 200 Amazon associates
- Communicate policies to my team and act as the primary information source for the team -maintaining compliance, consistency, and taking corrective action when needed
- Create, manage, and support recognition programs
- Support all safety programs and OSHA compliance to ensure a safe work environment for all associates
- Ensure procedures are followed for building security and product loss prevention
- Develop tools to track and analyze cost and production trends
- Partner with the management team to establish and maintain quality control standards
- Develop performance goals and objectives to achieve customer demand and ensure accuracy and quality

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

## **Altcademy**

- Full-Stack Deployment September 2022
- Ruby on Rails Certification July 2022

- Ruby Programming Certification June 2022
- ReactJS Development Certification June 2022

- Dynamic Website Development Certification -May 2022
- JavaScript Programming April 2022
- HTML CSS Development February 2022